webmyne.com 2019-05-31

# Qualified Lead Generation Company | Services | Solutions | Campaign - Webmyne.com

### Our Privacy Policy :

Your privacy is important to Webmyne and we are committed to protecting the privacy of parents and kids. Please take a moment to familiarize yourself with our privacy practices.

Webmyne uses and makes all attempts to protect all information when you use our apps & services.

If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use the service. We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy. If we make a material change to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting the change in this Privacy Policy. Please check back from time to time to ensure that you are aware of these changes. Your continued use of the Service will signify your acceptance of these changes.

### Personal Data Collected

We use technologies like cookies on our website (small files stored by your browser or operating system), web beacons, or unique device identifiers to anonymously identify your computer or device. Our systems also logs information like your browser, operating system, IP address and anonymous usage data so we can deliver a better experience. We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others.

### Data security

Webmyne uses reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of Users’ personal information.  
We take commercially reasonable efforts to maintain security protections in accordance with industry practices to protect data we collect from loss, alteration, destruction, misuse and unauthorized access or disclosure. 

### Non-personal Data

For purposes of this Privacy Policy, "non-personal data" means information that does not directly identify you. Additionally, non-personal data means "aggregate" and "de-personalized" information, which is data Webmyne collects about the use of Webmyne users, from which any personally identifiable data has been removed.

### App Store and Data Collection

We make the toddler focused games available via app stores such as Apple’s App Store, Google Play, Amazon AppStore, and Windows Store’s. While using the game, the App Store may use cookies, unique device identifier codes, software and hardware information, browser information, time zone and usage information or other technology to collect and process the information about you, and we may have access to it. We have no control over an App Store’s collection or use of information and cannot change what information the App Store makes available to us.

If you do not want to be subject to these technologies, do not use or access our Services.

### Children’s privacy

Webmyne does not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 years old or from websites or online services directed to children under 13 years old. Users should not create kids accounts unless they are legally old enough to form a binding contract and in any case are 13 years of age or older.

### Information Disclosure & Security

In the following circumstances, we may disclose your personal information according to your wish or regulations by law:

  * 1\. Your prior permission.
  * 2\. By the applicable law within or outside your country of residence, legal process, litigation requests.
  * 3\. By requests from public and governmental authorities.
  * 4\. To protect our legal rights and interests. We take reasonable steps to secure your information against unauthorized access or disclosure. We encrypt transmission of data on pages where you provide payment information. However, no security or encryption method can be guaranteed to protect information from hackers or human error.

### Applicable laws

Any relevant terms and conditions, policies and notices is governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of Vadodara Jurisdiction without giving effect to any principles of conflict of law. You hereby consent to the exclusive jurisdiction of the Court of Vadodara in respect of any legal disputes arising in connection with the website, or any relevant terms and conditions, policies and notices or any matter related to or in connection therewith Webmyne

### Contacting Us

If you have any questions regarding the Privacy Policy, please contact us at the following email address [ info@webmyne.com](mailto:info@webmyne.com)
